

+966 55 179 4989

wael.leb@live.com



7298 Al Watan - Dhahrat Laban SA, RIYADH 13784 - 4416

linkedin.com/in/waelhaydar



Retail Manager

Dedicated Retail Manager with 10+ years of experience in retail environments (frozen, dairy, grocery food, non-food, and fresh departments). Recognized for my ability to communicate with customers, provide exceptional service, and upsell products. Seeking retail management position with opportunities for advancement into a higher position.

EDUCATION

Technical School of Choueifat (2008–2010) BT3 Accounting & Informatics

WORK EXPERIENCE

La Carne Boutique (by Danat Al Alam), Riyadh, SA

International buyer grocery - store manager, February 2022 – July 2022

- Import
 - o Supplier communication and negotiation.
 - o Product registration in SFDA and regulations experience.
 - Clearance and shipping with local and foreign companies.
 - Pricing and labeling.

Tamimi Markets, Riyadh, SA

Fresh Food Manager - Assistant store manager - Express store manager, February 2019 – February 2022

- Excellent Customer Service
 - o involved in departments to provide excellent customer service
 - educate and train the department partners as an when required for customer service training
 - Department staff to always smile with customers, make eye contact and greet with offers and thank them
 - o Partner hygiene, as per our company sop
 - randomly visiting the department and checking with department staff for any issues or concerns in department.

- Merchandising
 - Product varieties availability
 - o Promo items availability
 - Receiving of products with high quality and maintaining display with Freshness rotation as per company sop
 - o Talking with supplier and pushing them to deliver what you need in store as per movement.
 - Distress control and identify the loop holes
 - o Inventory results full responsibility
 - check randomly invoice
 - SIDT
 - Distress
 - Delivery Product, quality, quantity and variety
 - o maintain daily Freshness rotation with quality and variety of products for customers choice
 - o responsible for inventory numbers
 - Maintain display standard
 - o Maintain cleanliness and hygiene environment in department to feel and look always fresh.

The Sultan Center, Beirut, LB

Department manager, March 2016-July 2017

AC Holding (SAMSUNG Lebanon), Beirut, LB

Retail Vendors Officer - After sales

- Customer Care Agent Retail vendors specific
 - o Receive and enter items need repair DATA to SAMSUNG systems
 - o check warranty validity according to provided documents
 - o answer every service-related inquiry
 - o contact dealers for any issue related to their and/or their customers repairs
 - invoicing
 - o report to AV and IT manager
- Repair Center Purchased Stock Control
 - o request stock to fix units with delayed parts as requested
 - o record all items received and follow-up until finished
 - return back finished units
- Pickup and Delivery
 - o send a driver daily to pick repairs from dealers' locations
 - o schedule drivers' pickups

KEY SKILLS

- · Expert organizational skills
- POS
- DATA analysis

- Upselling
- Excellent interpersonal skills
- Conflict resolution
- Time management